catererglobal.com 2017-06-17

# Privacy Policy | Catererglobal.com

At Catererglobal.com, we make every effort to comply with our obligations under the 1998 Data Protection Act.

Additionally, we understand the importance of maintaining the confidentiality of your CV and Profile, and other information you may give us while using the site. You can amend or delete any of the information that catererglobal.com stores about you by logging in to ‘My Account’ or by contacting us at [**customer.support@totaljobsgroup.com**](mailto:customer.support@totaljobsgroup.com) with your request.

Catererglobal.com is part of the Total Jobs Group Ltd group of websites and of the StepStone GmbH group of companies (the "StepStone Group"). StepStone is a global online job board company that operates online job portals to accurately match candidates with companies.

**Profile and CV information**

Contact and other details you supply as part of the registration process are stored by us and used to provide you with the information you have requested.

When you complete your catererglobal.com profile, it may be made available for searching, viewing over the Internet, including other company recruitment sites within the StepStone Group, and downloading by catererglobal.com’s or any customer of the StepStone Group. Customers that request details of candidates with your type of profile, may be sent your profile by email.

These may be direct recruiters, employment consultants or other organisations.

Your CV can be uploaded as part of an online application. Therefore this will be sent to the employer that you choose to send it to. The CV will be kept electronically by us or another company within the StepStone Group, and may be viewed by employers.

When registering your profile, you can choose to prevent our customers from accessing your personal details and profile.

IMPORTANT: Your current employer may be a customer of catererglobal.com, or a client of one of our consultancy customers. Catererglobal.com cannot restrict the customers who access profiles on our database and cannot be held responsible for any eventuality. As part of the registration process catererglobal.com offers you the option of remaining anonymous.

Catererglobal.com will also use the aggregate data to identify trends, such as salary averages and experience/skills levels.

If you choose to create a profile and upload a CV to our database, we rely on you to ensure that your details are kept up to date. You should update your CV at least every six months, particularly if your contact details have changed. Once your profile and CV are on our database we will contact you every six months using your most recent contact details to ask whether you want it to remain there. If we do not hear from you, your profile and CV will be removed from our database.

Please note that catererglobal.com reserves the right to remove from our database CVs which include any content that we consider to be illegal or offensive. We will also remove a CV if a complaint is upheld, which has been made against it.

**Sharing Your Information**

Personal data which you supply to us may be transferred to third party service providers to be stored or processed on our behalf, including third parties located outside of the European Economic Area in countries where there may be a lower legal level of data protection. However, we will always endeavour to handle your information in accordance with this privacy policy, wherever it is processed.

Personal data which we collect from both public sources and from yourself may also be shared with other companies within the StepStone Group. This may include your job seeker profile and result in your profile being searchable on other company sites within the StepStone Group. At all times, the StepStone Group companies will ensure that your information is adequately protected. Each member of the StepStone Group may use and share your personal information as set out in this privacy policy. In accordance with the type of services you have registered for, requested, and the functionality you use, we will disclose your personal information for a prospective job.

**Cookies**

Cookies are small pieces of information stored by us on your computer which enable us to identify your computer when you access the catererglobal.com web site and to provide you with a convenient means of access. The cookies we use also protect the integrity of registered user names and passwords. We also use cookies to collect aggregate statistical information about the use of our site (see Statistical information below).

There is no personally identifiable information held on cookies. An example of a cookie is below.

10.20.25.21- 2020212848.29592612::413EA8A33A38AC8CCE09CC624E8B4758

You have the option to decline or accept these cookies, but if you decline you will not be able to access the personalised areas of the site. This means you will not be able to access your candidate profile, apply online or set up any ‘jobs by email’ requests.

We strongly recommend you accept cookies.

In addition, the third party companies who sell and provide advertisements to the site, and host our contacts database, make use of cookies for the purpose of serving and targeting advertisements more effectively. For more information about these cookies, how you can opt out of receiving them and how this will affect your use of web sites in general, please visit the websites of our third party suppliers: [**Adtech**](http://www.adtech.info/privacy_en.php) and [**Bluestreak**](http://www.bluestreak.com/).

**Statistical information**

We provide aggregate statistical information about site visitors and users to recruiters (such as the number of CVs on the database, or the number of visitors to the site) and for other lawful purposes. We provide this information to customers, advertisers, suppliers and other reputable third parties. This will not include any information that enables them to identify individuals.

**Security**

The site is protected against unauthorised access using the latest security devices and 'firewalls' – hosted by Madgex Ltd.
